Guide to the KUHT Records 1997-006
University of Houston Libraries Special Collections
- KUHT Production Files
  - Video Files
    - Live at the Woodlands - Equipment (Box 429, Folder 18)
    - Live at the Woodlands - FACs, Shipping Reports (Box 429, Folder 19)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Front Row Productions (Box 429, Folder 20)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Hotels (Box 429, Folder 21)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Insurance (Box 429, Folder 22)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Insurance, Letter of Agreement (Box 429, Folder 23)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Invoices (Box 429, Folder 24)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Invoices, Requisitions (Box 429, Folder 25)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Licensing Contracts (Box 429, Folder 26)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Logo (Box 429, Folder 27)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Logo, Graphics (Box 429, Folder 28)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Lovett Logs (Box 429, Folder 29)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Maps (Box 429, Folder 30)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Memos, Faxes (Box 429, Folder 31)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Memos, from Jim Fischer (Box 429, Folder 32)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Meetings (Box 429, Folder 33)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Miscellaneous (Box 429, Folder 34-36)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Post (Box 429, Folder 37)
    - Live at the Woodlands - June 27 Post Mortem (Box 429, Folder 38)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Press (Box 429, Folder 39)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Program Formats, Ideas (Box 429, Folder 40)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Proposal (Box 429, Folder 41)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Public Relations (Box 429, Folder 42)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Sample Invoice (Box 429, Folder 43)
    - Live at the Woodlands - June 27 Schedule of the Day (Box 429, Folder 44)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Schedules (Box 429, Folder 45)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Talent Contract (Box 429, Folder 46)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Vendor Information (Box 429, Folder 47)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Video Truck (Box 429, Folder 48)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Volunteers, P.A.S., Office Supplies (Box 429, Folder 49)
    - Living with AIDS - National Press Kit (Box 430, Folder 1)
    - A Long Journey Home (Box 430, Folder 2)
    - Lorenz-Evans Transcript (Box 430, Folder 3-4)
    - Madame Scandal (Box 430, Folder 5)
    - Making the Grade (Box 430, Folder 6)
    - Marrot Communications (Box 430, Folder 7)
    - Masters (Box 430, Folder 8)
    - Matter of Time (Box 430, Folder 9)
    - Mathews, Corey 364-1217 (Box 430, Folder 10)
    - Medicine and the Modern Woman (Box 430, Folder 11)
    - Meet the Candidates (Box 430, Folder 12)
    - Membership March - Festival Workshop, 1984 (Box 430, Folder 13)
    - Membership March - Festival Workshop, 1985 (Box 430, Folder 14)
    - Membership March - Membership Material, 1985-1989 (Box 430, Folder 15-16)
    - Membership March, 1990 (Box 430, Folder 17-18)
    - Membership March, 1995 (Box 430, Folder 19-20)
    - Membership March, 1995 (Box 431, Folder 1)
    - Membership March, August 12-13, 1995 (Box 431, Folder 2)
    - Membership March, September 1995 (Box 431, Folder 3)
    - Membership March - R & R, August 3, 1996 (Box 431, Folder 4)
    - Membership March - 3 Tenors, October 26, 1996 (Box 431, Folder 5)
    - Membership March, 1997 (Box 431, Folder 6-8)
    - Membership March - Pledge, 1997 (Box 431, Folder 9)
    - Membership March - Toolbox (Box 431, Folder 10-11)
    - Mending of Man (Box 431, Folder 12)
    - Messiah (Box 431, Folder 13)
    - Milt Larkin's Rhumboogie Retrospective (Box 431, Folder 14)
    - Money Show (Box 431, Folder 15)
    - Moore, John; Kren, Kurt; Yeager, Paul (Box 431, Folder 16)
    - Most Endangered Species - Dr. Denton Cooley (Box 431, Folder 17)
    - Most Endangered Species - George Adamson (Box 431, Folder 18)
    - NASA Teacher Flight (Box 431, Folder 19)
    - National Geographic (Box 431, Folder 20)
    - Nature of Texas (Box 431, Folder 21)
    - Neeld, Elizabeth Harper (Box 431, Folder 22)
    - Netherlands/Texas Cultural Exhange Project (Box 431, Folder 23)
    - New Gospel Jubilee (Box 431, Folder 24)
    - A New Renaissance (Box 431, Folder 25)
    - Norway (Box 432, Folder 1)
    - Norway - Transcript #1, Original (Box 432, Folder 2-4)
    - Norway - Transcript #2, Original (Box 432, Folder 5-6)
    - Nuevas Visiones/New Visions (Box 432, Folder 7)
    - Oil Across Water (Box 432, Folder 8)
    - Old Secrets (Box 432, Folder 9)
    - On The Record - Roberta Hammond (Box 432, Folder 10)
    - On The Record - Susan Wright (Box 432, Folder 11)
    - Opera New World, December 1992 (Box 432, Folder 12)
    - One of the Missing (Box 432, Folder 13-14)
    - One Wish - Virtual Love (Box 432, Folder 15)
    - Our Elderly at Stake (Box 432, Folder 16)
    - Pakistan Project with John Ahrens (Box 432, Folder 17)
    - Patty - Clean Script, Pilot (Box 432, Folder 18)
    - Patty - Correspondence (Box 432, Folder 19)
    - Patty - Girls Selected (Box 432, Folder 20)
    - Patty - Girls Not Selected (Box 432, Folder 21)
    - Patty - Releases (Box 432, Folder 22)
    - Performing Arts, Theaters (Box 432, Folder 23)
    - Piaf, Brel and Le Brun (Box 432, Folder 24)
    - Play it Safe (Box 432, Folder 25)
    - Postal Regulations, Addressing (Box 432, Folder 26)
    - Presley, Elvis (Box 432, Folder 27)
    - Profiles from Houston - Horton Foote (Box 432, Folder 28)
    - Psychiatry, 1991 (Box 433, Folder 1)
    - Psychiatry, 1992 (Box 433, Folder 2)
    - Psychiatry: Helping and Healing, 1988-1989 (Box 433, Folder 3)
    - Psychiatry: Helping Families Heal, Fall 1991 (Box 433, Folder 4)
    - Psychiatry: Helping Families Heal from Divorce (Box 433, Folder 5)
    - A Question of Color (Box 433, Folder 6)
    - Ramses II: Glorious Pharoah (Box 433, Folder 7)
    - The Ranchers: Born to this Land (Box 433, Folder 8)
    - Reading Rainbow Contest (Box 433, Folder 9)
    - Real Life - Kym King (Box 433, Folder 10)
    - Redistricting Houston with Betti Maldonado (Box 433, Folder 11)
    - Reina De La Selva (Box 433, Folder 12-13)
    - Report Card: The State of Our Schools (Box 433, Folder 14)
    - Return to HEPU: Li Tim-Oi Goes Home (Box 433, Folder 15)
    - Ribbons of Life (Box 433, Folder 16)
    - Rivers of Innocence (Box 433, Folder 17)
    - Ryan's Roundtable (Box 433, Folder 18)
    - Save the Males: An Endangered Species (Box 433, Folder 19)
    - Screenwriters Houston (Box 433, Folder 20)
    - Sesame in Austin (Box 433, Folder 21)
    - Shade of Truth, March 1993 (Box 433, Folder 22)
    - Shakespeare Rides Again (Box 433, Folder 23)
    - Shoplifting (Box 433, Folder 24)
    - Singing with Cindy, 1981 (Box 433, Folder 25)
    - Smith, Dr. Arthur K. - Investiture (Box 433, Folder 26-29)
    - Smithsonian (Box 434, Folder 1)
    - Something Out of Nothing (Box 434, Folder 2-3)
    - S.O.S. Journal Local (Box 434, Folder 4)
    - South Africa: A Bright Hope (Box 434, Folder 5)
    - The South Orient Express (Box 434, Folder 6)
    - Southwest Alternate Media Project (Box 434, Folder 7)
    - Spacewatch (Box 434, Folder 8-9)
    - Spacewatch - Publicity (Box 434, Folder 10-11)
    - Spacewatch - Slides, Photos (Box 434, Folder 12)
    - Sports Unlimited (Box 434, Folder 13)
    - Storms Warnings, Underground (Box 434, Folder 14)
    - Studio 8 - Promotion (Box 434, Folder 15)
    - A Teacher's Journey Through Space (Box 434, Folder 16)
    - Tear Down the Walls (Box 434, Folder 17)
    - Tennis (Box 434, Folder 18)
    - Territory (Box 434, Folder 19-21)
    - Territory - 15 Years Later (Swamp) (Box 434, Folder 22)
    - Territory - 1700, October 10, 1992 (Box 434, Folder 23)
    - Territory - Media Project (Box 434, Folder 24)
    - Territory - Season 21 (Box 434, Folder 25)
    - Territory - This State I'm In (Box 435, Folder 1)
    - Texas Rangers (Box 435, Folder 2-3)
    - This State I'm In - 1 sheet (Box 435, Folder 4)
    - The Time of Her Life (Box 435, Folder 5)
    - T.L.L. Temple Foundation Awards Press Release (Box 435, Folder 6)
    - Town Meeting - #1 HPD Community Relations Project (Box 435, Folder 7-8)
    - Town Meeting - #2 People vs. Crime (Box 435, Folder 9-10)
    - Town Meeting - #2 People vs. Crime, Transcripts (Box 435, Folder 11-14)
    - Town Meeting - #3 Report Card (Box 435, Folder 15-16)
    - Town Meeting - #201 The Evolving Family - Todd Hewey, November 21, 1991 (Box 436, Folder 1-2)
    - Town Meeting - #202 Aging (Box 436, Folder 3-6)
    - Town Meeting - #202 Aging, Transcripts (Box 436, Folder 7-12)
    - Town Meeting - #203 Our Children: Casualties of American Culture, May 20, 1992 (Box 436, Folder 13-15)
    - Town Meeting - #203 Our Children: Casualties of American Culture, May 20, 1992 (Box 437, Folder 1-4)
    - Town Meeting - #301 Created Equal? (Box 437, Folder 5)
    - Town Meeting - #301 Racism (Box 437, Folder 6)
    - Town Meeting - #301 Racism, Transcripts (Box 437, Folder 7-12)
    - Town Meeting - #302 Immigration (Box 437, Folder 13)
    - Town Meeting - #303 Violence (Box 437, Folder 14)
    - Town Meeting - #307 Racism (Box 437, Folder 15-16)
    - Town Meeting - #307 Racism, Transcripts (Box 437, Folder 17-18)
    - Town Meeting - #307 Racism, Transcripts (Box 438, Folder 1-3)
    - Town Meeting - #401 Prescription for Reform (Box 438, Folder 4)
    - Town Meeting - #402 Generation at Risk (Box 438, Folder 5)
    - Town Meeting - Baby Boomers and Beyond (Box 438, Folder 6)
    - Town Meeting - Condition Critical: Health Care in Harris County (Box 438, Folder 7)
    - Town Meeting - Family at Risk (Box 438, Folder 8)
    - Town Meeting - Generation at Risk (Box 438, Folder 9)
    - Town Meeting - Health Care Reform (Box 438, Folder 10)
    - Town Meeting - Immigration (Box 438, Folder 11)
    - Town Meeting - Local (Box 438, Folder 12)
    - Town Meeting - Our Children (Box 438, Folder 13)
    - Town Meeting - People vs. Crime (Box 438, Folder 14)
    - Town Meeting - Race (Box 438, Folder 15)
    - Town Meeting - Racism, October 1992 (Box 438, Folder 16)
    - Town Meeting - Teen Issues, May 1994 (Box 438, Folder 17)
    - Town Meeting - The Evolving Family (Box 438, Folder 18)
    - Town Meeting - This Life Rated 'R' for Violence (Box 438, Folder 19)
    - Town Meeting - Threads in the Fabric (Box 438, Folder 20)
    - Town Meeting - Violence (Box 438, Folder 21)
    - Town Meeting - Youth Violence (Box 438, Folder 22)
    - Turtles II (Box 438, Folder 23)
    - University of Houston - Faculty Experts (Box 438, Folder 24)
    - Vachss, Andrew (Box 438, Folder 25)
    - VCR Semester (Box 438, Folder 26)
    - Video Heads (Box 438, Folder 27)
    - Video Tape Logs (Box 438, Folder 28)
    - Vietnam: A Season of Healing (Box 438, Folder 29)
    - Vietnam Project (Box 438, Folder 30-33)
    - Viking and Western (Box 439, Folder 1)
    - Voyage from Antiquity (Box 439, Folder 2)
    - We Beat Thailand...Education on the Edge (Box 439, Folder 3)
    - Weeknight Edition - Press Release (Box 439, Folder 4)
    - Whence Turtles Come (Box 439, Folder 5)
    - Who Killed Fourth Ward (Box 439, Folder 6)
    - 40,000 Window Panes (Box 439, Folder 7)
    - Window on the War (Box 439, Folder 8-10)
    - A World Transformed (Box 439, Folder 11-15)
    - A World Transformed - Transcripts (Box 439, Folder 16-18)
    - Wortham (Box 439, Folder 19)
    - The Yarn Spinner, Bill Brett (Box 439, Folder 20)
    - Yatri, The Traveler (Box 439, Folder 21)
- Photographs and Slides
  This series contains photographs of several major auctions which KUHT used to raise funds and to promote the television station. The photographs are arranged chronologically.
  - Negatives, 1953 (Box 440, Folder 1)
    - Stills from filming in classroom (8), 1953
  - 60-5 Civil Defense Production Stills, 1960 (Box 440, Folder 2)
  - 61-8 "Insight" Museum of Fine Arts - Logs, Stills, 1961 (Box 440, Folder 3)
  - 64-1 Foundation of Hope - Stills, Proofs (Box 440, Folder 4)
  - 65-3 The Chamizal, 1965 (Box 440, Folder 5)
    - Stills from filming The Chamizal (8), including LBJ at event, 1965
  - 65-8 The Healing Truth, 1965 (Box 440, Folder 6)
  - 66-5 Brain Damaged Children - Proofs, 1966 (Box 440, Folder 7)
  - Youth, 1970 (Box 440, Folder 8)
    - Drugs: Use and Abuse pamphlet, 1970
    - Drugs: Use and Abuse film stills (4), 1970
  - Auction, 1971 (Box 440, Folder 9)
  - 71-24 Battle of Waterloo - Production Stills, 1971 (Box 440, Folder 10)
  - Viewpoint, January 10, 1973 (Box 440, Folder 11)
  - Auction Promos, 1973 (Box 440, Folder 12)
  - Auction Promos and Activities, 1973-1974 (Box 440, Folder 13)
  - Auction, 1974 (Box 440, Folder 14)
  - Signing with Cindy, 1974 (Box 440, Folder 15)
  - Thanksgiving Parade, 1974 (Box 440, Folder 16)
  - ACT, Art Auction Committee, 1975 (Box 440, Folder 17)
  - Children's Bookshelf, Fall/Winter 1975 (Box 440, Folder 18)
  - Summer ACT Festival, 1975 (Box 440, Folder 19)
  - Thanksgiving Parade, 1975 (Box 440, Folder 20)
  - Ben Woitena & Sculptor, January 28, 1976 (Box 440, Folder 21)
  - Auction B&W, 1976 (Box 440, Folder 22)
  - Mr. Rogers & Thanksgiving Parade, 1976 (Box 440, Folder 23)
    - Mr. Rogers On Set negatives (24), 1976
  - Program Guide, 1976 (Box 440, Folder 24)
  - Auction Parties, 1976-1977 (Box 440, Folder 25)
  - Auction, 1977 (Box 440, Folder 26)
  - Auction Chairman, 1977 (Box 440, Folder 27)
  - Friday Night Local, 1977 (Box 440, Folder 28)
  - Greenroom, 1977 (Box 440, Folder 29)
  - Minority Report, 1977 (Box 440, Folder 30)
  - Progressive Pick in 1977 (Box 440, Folder 31)
  - 25th Show with Dick Cavett & Ella Fitzgerald, May 25, 1978 (Box 440, Folder 32)
    - Dick Cavett negatives (32), May 25, 1978
  - The Skinner Interview 1978, c/o Dan Rodgers, Director, July 26, 1978 (Box 440, Folder 33)
    - B.F. Skinner Interview negatives (17), July 26, 1978
  - August Membership Drive, 1978 (Box 440, Folder 34)
  - Christmas Harp Special c/o Liz, August 17, 1978 (Box 440, Folder 35)
  - A Matter of Time - The Harvest Years, September 1978 (Box 440, Folder 36)
  - PTV - Potpourri 1978, October 3, 1978 (Box 440, Folder 37)
  - Jazz Dance Special 1978, October 19, 1978 (Box 440, Folder 38)
  - 25th Party, October 29, 1978 (Box 440, Folder 39)
  - Membership Drive, December 1978 (Box 440, Folder 40)
  - ACT Auction, 1978 (Box 440, Folder 41)
  - ACT Awards, 1978 (Box 440, Folder 42)
  - Auction, 1978 (Box 440, Folder 43)
  - Auction Awards, 1978 (Box 440, Folder 44)
  - Auction Chairman, 1978 (Box 440, Folder 45)
  - Auction Art Chairman, Carol Strauss, 1978 (Box 440, Folder 46)
  - Auction Donation, 1978 (Box 440, Folder 47)
  - Auction Parties, 1978 (Box 440, Folder 48)
  - Auction Townhouse, 1978 (Box 440, Folder 49)
  - The Greenroom 1978 Season (Box 440, Folder 50)
  - GRETA Book Covers, 1978 (Box 441, Folder 1)
  - Interchange Charles Porter Portrait Set, 1978 (Box 441, Folder 2)
  - Membership Chairman, 1978 (Box 441, Folder 3)
  - News Information, 1978 (Box 441, Folder 4)
  - Program Guide Cover Shots, 1978 (Box 441, Folder 5)
  - Rosewood & Silver, 1978 (Box 441, Folder 6)
  - Season B&W Set Division Weekly Shows, 1978 (Box 441, Folder 7)
  - Sports Unlimited Fall Season, 1978 (Box 441, Folder 8)
  - Vienna Prelude, 1978 (Box 441, Folder 9)
  - Viesta Elma Barns Set Photos, 1978 (Box 441, Folder 10)
  - Subaru Brat Auction 1979, January 16, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 11)
  - Shakespeare Festival, February 1979 (Box 441, Folder 12)
  - Chinese Vice Premier - Teng Hsaou visit to US, Houston, February 2, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 13)
    - Vice Premier Teng Hsiao Ping arriving in Houston negatives (20), February 2, 1979
  - GRETA 1979, February 14, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 14)
  - Lionel Father & Son Tennis, February 17-18, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 15)
  - Membership, March 1979 (Box 441, Folder 16)
  - Auction Disco Party, March 24, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 17)
  - ACT Board Meeting Luncheon Awards, May 1979 (Box 441, Folder 18)
  - Friday Local Gov. Clenninos, May 1979 (Box 441, Folder 19)
  - McNeil & Lehrer, George Bush, May 1979 (Box 441, Folder 20)
    - George Bush negatives (20), May 1979
  - San Francisco Mime Troupe, May 1979 (Box 441, Folder 21)
  - The Sound of Pan, May 26, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 22)
  - The Week, Host John Daucaport, June 28, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 23)
  - Membership Products, July 3, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 24)
  - Public Information, Special on Skylab - Departures on Tape, July 10, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 25)
  - 1980 Auction Chairman, Carroll Ann Paddock, July 19, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 26)
  - Auction Promotion - Miller Theater Concert Dedication, July 19, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 27)
  - General Homes President Joe de George & Big Bird Announce "GH" Underwriting in October, July 20, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 28)
    - Big Bird receives support check for Channel 8 negatives (10), July 20, 1979
  - Area Auction Chairman, July 26, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 29)
  - Greta's New Building, August 1979 (Box 441, Folder 30)
  - Membership, August 26, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 31)
  - No Room at the Park, August 26, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 32)
  - Graphics Van, September 1979 (Box 441, Folder 33)
  - McNeil & Lehrer - Charleen, Sept. 1979 (Box 441, Folder 34)
  - Membership Luncheon Awards, September 1979 (Box 441, Folder 35)
  - Asst. Chairman - Auction, September 6, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 36)
  - Greenroom Houston Ballet Giselle, September 27, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 37)
  - George Collins' Last Day, Retired, 25 years, September 28, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 38)
  - The Greenroom - Alley Opening & Jones Hall Opera's Opening, October 18, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 39)
  - Interchange Reggae Band & Dances, October 23, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 40)
  - La Voz Betty Maldonado, October 23, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 41)
  - Special Productions Studio Sets, November 2, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 42)
  - 1980 Auction, John Pace, November 5, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 43)
  - Sports Unlimited, November 6, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 44)
  - La Voz Set & Production Shots with Betty, November 7, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 45)
  - Thanksgiving Parade, November 20, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 46)
  - Membership Drive, December 1979 (Box 441, Folder 47)
  - First Opening Program - KUHT, Copied, December 12, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 48)
  - The Greenroom Charles Dickens, December 15, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 49)
  - Auction, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 50)
  - Auction - Go-Getters, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 51-52)
  - Auction - Items, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 53)
  - Auction - People Involved in Putting it Together, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 54)
  - Congressman Ron Paul, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 55)
  - The Greenroom, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 56)
  - Jack Ellis Cowboy Ad for Texas Monthly for Auction, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 57)
  - The KUHT Auction, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 58)
  - Lionel Tennis Tournament Opening & Closing Creeks Backgroud Shots, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 59)
  - PTV Potpourri, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 60)
  - Public Information, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 61)
  - Staff Photographs, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 62)
  - #1880 Auction Art Committee, Dan R., January 8, 1980 (Box 441, Folder 63)
  - #1980 Transmitter Alvin, Texas, Bruce Swee, Dan R., January 9, 1980 (Box 441, Folder 64)
  - #2095 The 1980 Auction May Volunteers and Staff, photo: Dan R., January 10, 1980 (Box 441, Folder 65)
  - #11980 New Immigrants, Mim Kirshak, January 19, 1980 (Box 441, Folder 66)
  - #21180 Auction Specials Party, Dan R., Texas Tin Horn, February 11, 1980 (Box 441, Folder 67)
  - #21980 Civilization I.D. Slide, Dan Richardson, February 19, 1980 (Box 441, Folder 68)
  - #1910 Mystery I.D. Slide, Dan Richardson, February 19, 1980 (Box 441, Folder 69)
  - #1970 Interchange Former F.C.C. Commissioner Benjamin Hooks, Dan Richardson, February 22, 1980 (Box 441, Folder 70)
  - #1983 Chinese Consulate Office, Dan Richardson - China Film Prep., February 25, 1980 (Box 441, Folder 71)
  - #1859 La Voz Jazz Band, Brazilian Express, Dan Richardson, February 25, 1980 (Box 441, Folder 72)
  - #1990 China Film Trip, Mayor's Office, Dan Richardson, Liz Kaderli, February 28, 1980 (Box 441, Folder 73)
  - #1983, Membership, Mayor's Office Proclamation Ceremony, Dan Richardson, February 28, 1980 (Box 441, Folder 74)
  - #2281 Piaf, Brel & LeBrun, Promotion Slide, Dan Richardson, February 29, 1980 (Box 441, Folder 75)
  - #2000 Membership Drives, photo: Dan Richardson, March 1-16, 1980 (Box 441, Folder 76)
  - #2001 Houston Rodeo, photo: Dan Richardson, March 2, 1980 (Box 441, Folder 77)
  - #1978 Auction Preview Insert, March 7, 1980 (Box 441, Folder 78)
  - #2008 Julia Child, photo: Dan Richardson, March 12, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 1)
    - Julia Child with Channel 8 10th Anniversary cake, March 12, 1980
    - Julia Child with Channel 8 10th Anniversary cake, March 12, 1980
    - Julia Child with book, March 12, 1980
  - #2003 Auction Volunteer Party, photo: Dan Richardson, March 21, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 2)
  - #2017 Carnaval, Unidos de Austin, photo: Dan Richardson, March 22, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 3)
  - #2029 Armenians Remember, photo: Dan Richardson, March 24, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 4)
  - #1991 Auction G.H.B.A. Home in Cimarron, photo: Dan Richardson, March 30, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 5)
  - #2083 Development Target Stores, Dan Fuester @ David Garrison, photo: Dan Richardson, April 1980 (Box 442, Folder 6)
  - #2061 Auction David Adickes, photo: Dan Richardson, April 10, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 7)
  - #2077 Auction Lynn Wyatt & Bob Sakowits, photo: Dan Richardson, April 14, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 8)
  - #1993 Auction Art Preview Party @ Art Set Up; photo: Dan Richardson, April 16, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 9)
  - #2070 La Voz Latina - Jesús Negrete, photo: Dan Richardson, April 16, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 10)
  - #2100 Development - JJ Monkeyshines, photo: Dan Richardson, April 30, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 11)
  - #2105 Fever - Glenn McCarthy @ John Davenport, photo: Dan Richardson, May 9, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 12)
  - #2153 GRETA ID Slides, graphics: Dan Richardson, June 10, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 13)
  - #2181 Membership Houston Opera Company Theater, photo: Dan Richardson, July 2, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 14)
  - #2190 Development Conoco-Turtles, photo: Bob Balazik, July 8, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 15)
  - #2189 Development First City National Bank, Mr. Rogers, David Lane, July 9, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 16)
  - #2197 Piaf, Brel & LeBrun, photo: Dan Richardson, July 9, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 17)
  - #2192 Membership Drive Products, photo: Bob Balazik, July 14, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 18)
  - #2205 Auction First 1981 Auction, Central Meeting, photo: Dan Richardson, July 18, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 19)
  - #2215 Auction - Area Chairman, Auction - 1981, photo: Dan Richardson, July 18, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 20)
  - #2220 KUHT - graphics ID: Dan Richardson, July 18, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 21)
  - #2222 Auction GHBA, Rollie McGinnis-John Pace, photo: Dan Richardson, July 21, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 22)
  - #2218 Membership Promotion Material Roll Photo, photo: Dan Richardson, July 24, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 23)
  - #2237 Fluor Check Presentation, Jim Bauer, Joe Passmore, photo: Dan Richardson, July 31, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 24)
  - #2251 Remote Truck, photo: Dan Richardson, August 4, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 25)
  - #2268 Lawyer to Layman, Copy Negative, August 14, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 26)
  - #2276 War at Peace, photo: Bob Balazik, August 18, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 27)
  - #2268 Lawyer to Layman, art: Jack Ellis, photo: Dan Richardson, August 29, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 28)
  - #2297 Lawyer to Layman, photo: Dan Richardson, August 29, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 29)
  - #2282 Piaf, Brel & LeBrun, the screening photo: Dan Richardson, September 4, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 30)
  - #2294 Projection 80, photo: Dan Richardson (Box 442, Folder 31)
  - #2297 Mitt Larkins Rhumboogie, photo: Dan Richardson, September 9, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 32)
  - #2302 Wine Tasting, Maria Newman, Fran Buckmaster, Bob Whickman - G.M. of Hacienda Debs Morale, September 10, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 33)